Vattandeep Kaur



vattandeep8@gmail.com | +918557044500 | Punjab http://linkedin.com/in/vattandeep-kaur-8844001ab https://github.com/Vattandeep

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

A skillful Social Media professional with an experience of 7 years in corporate as well as government sector. Proven ability to assess and manage the work load in odd situations, Strong verbal skills, critical thinking, adaptability, leadership qualities, time management. Worked as a content writer for CM of the state. Experienced in MS Excel, MySQL, Tableau, Power BI, VBA, Pandas, Numpy.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Excel | Power BI | MySQL | VBA and Macros | Pandas | Numpy | Seaborn | Dashboard | Github | Matplotlib | Mixpad Multitrack Recording Software | Tableau | FCP and Adobe Premiere Pro | Canvas | Corel Draw | Quark Express | Adobe Page Maker

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Directorate of Information and Public Relations, Govt. of Punjab

Sector-1, Chandigarh

Content Writer

Since March 1, 2021 Till Date

Creating content for the posts of Social Media handles, all types of hoardings & website along with the scripts for the audio/video advertisements of **Government of Punjab**.

Worked in the CM's personal **Social Media Team for S. Charanjit Singh Channi**, Former Chief Minister of Punjab. There I also wrote slogans for his political campaign.

Daily Charhdikala

Sub Editor cum Content Writer

Patiala, Punjab Sept. 2017 – Jan 2021

- Writing News and Articles for Charhdikala Newspaper; Translation.
- Creating and Proof Reading Content for Magazine; Page Making.

INTERNSHIP

Rozana Spokesman

Intern cum Sub-Editor

Phase-1, Mohali June 2016- July 2016

- Writing & editing News stories and Articles for the newspaper
- Designing the page of newspaper

PROJECTS

Python - Descriptive Statistics

Project of MySQL Project of Power BI Project of Ms Excel

Campaign Name-

Mission Fateh (Covid-19) | Rangla Punjab | Invest Punjab | Azadi Ka Amrit Mahotsav | Mohalla Clinics | Stubble Burning | No. 1 Punjab (Education) | Khedan Watan Punjab Diyan |

https://new.express.adobe.com/publishedV2/urn:aaid:sc:AP:1231916b-a316-406a-b0aa-126f9fcc40f7?promoid=Y69SGM5H&mv=other

- Campaigns run by DIPR, Govt. of Punjab

Departments worked with - Tourism and Cultural Affairs | Water Supply and Sanitation | Food, Civil Supplies and Consumer Affairs | Health | School Education | Health and Family Welfare | Social Security and Development of Women & Children | Rural Development and Panchayats | Agriculture

EDUCATION

| Punjabi | Univ | ersity, I | 'atiala |
|---------|------|-----------|---------|
| | O T | 1. | 1 1 7 |

Patiala 2 Years

Masters of Journalism and Mass Communication 74%

Govt. Mohindra College/ Govt. Clg. Malerkotla

Patiala/Malerkotla

3 Years

51%

GSSS (Girls), Bhawanigarh

Bachelors of Science

Bhawanigarh

1 Year

12th 60%

Saint Soldier Public High School 10th

Bhawanigarh
1 Year

80%

2